<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Komodo Blogs</title>
        <description>Komodo blog RSS feed.  </description>
        <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/</link>
        <language>en</language>
        <webMaster>support@activestate.com (ActiveState Support)</webMaster>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 09:03:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Middleman 3.3.10</generator>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 10.1 Beta Now Available</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-1-beta-now-available</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>The Komodo 10.1 beta is now available. This is a big update that focusses primarily on what our community has been asking us for. Over 100 bugs were fixed and more will be addressed before this release turns stable [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-1-beta-now-available</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>HotKey Conundrum</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/hotkey-conundrum</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>As you may know by now (or maybe you don&#x27;t, which is ok since I&#x27;m going to follow up by stating the fact anyway...), Komodo has been in development for over 15 years now [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/hotkey-conundrum</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Case Study: Lua Debugging in Komodo</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/case-study-lua-debugging-in-komodo</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>I had thoughts about trying something crazy with Komodo...so when ActiveState held its annual hackathon I saw it as a great opportunity for me to try out one of these ideas. Before I jump into what I did [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/case-study-lua-debugging-in-komodo</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>The Advantage of Komodo&#x27;s Editor Over JavaScript Based Editors</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/the-advantage-of-komodos-editor-over-javascript-based-editors</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 3 Aug 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Nowadays, it seems that IDEs and text editors are to software developers as sports cars are to car enthusiasts. Ask any developer what tool they use to write their code and why, and you will get a million different answers [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/the-advantage-of-komodos-editor-over-javascript-based-editors</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Go to Any Symbol With Komodo&#x27;s New Symbol Browser</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/go-to-any-symbol-with-komodos-new-symbol-browser</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>As an IDE, one of the features that Komodo must have and must do well (IMO) is code intelligence. It MUST help you understand the code your working on more quickly (even if...ESPECIALLY IF it&#x27;s yours) [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/go-to-any-symbol-with-komodos-new-symbol-browser</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Filling the Gap with Commandline Integration - PhoneGap, Cordova, Grunt, Gulp</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/filling-the-gap-with-commandline-integration-phonegap-cordova-grunt-gulp</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Something that has always been part of the Komodo design philosophy has been integration. Though Komodo should provide tooling to make our users more productive, it should NOT try to do EVERYTHING.  Integration, not imitation, is the key [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/filling-the-gap-with-commandline-integration-phonegap-cordova-grunt-gulp</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>First Start Wizard</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/first-start-wizard</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>If you&#x27;ve never run Komodo before or if this is the first time you&#x27;re running a major version (eg. you were using Komodo 9.3 and have just upgraded to Komodo X), then Komodo will show you the First Start Wizard as it loads [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/first-start-wizard</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Under the Hood: Komodo X and Chrome Debugging</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/under-the-hood-komodo-x-and-chrome-debugging</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>It is easy to take for granted Komodo IDE&#x27;s superb debugging support. Komodo excels at debugging common scripting languages like Perl, Python, Tcl, and Ruby. It can also debug PHP, Node.js, and XSLT. With Komodo X [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/under-the-hood-komodo-x-and-chrome-debugging</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Extreme Makeover</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-extreme-makeover</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 6 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>If you installed Komodo X recently and you were not one of the users who participated in the Beta release phase then when you opened Komodo you might have thought you downloaded the wrong program (Chess any one?).  But you didn&#x27;t [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-extreme-makeover</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>10 Komodo Features Web Developers Will Love</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/10-komodo-features-web-developers-will-love</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo IDE X adds a ton of new features, many of which targeted at web developers. We realize that while not everyone may consider themselves a web developer, most developers these days will be using web technologies to some degree [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/10-komodo-features-web-developers-will-love</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>How We Made Komodo X Even Faster</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/how-we-made-komodo-x-even-faster</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo has always been a very fast IDE. So much so that combined with its minimalistic UI many users tend to confuse Komodo IDE with an editor. Of course Komodo is an editor too, but to call it just an editor would be doing it a disservice [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/how-we-made-komodo-x-even-faster</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 10.0.1 Released</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-0-1-released</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>We hope everyone has been enjoying Komodo X so far. Today we&#x27;re releasing our first update, which is focussed entirely on stability and primarily resolves bugs introduced in 10.0.0 as well as a few longer standing issues [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-0-1-released</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo X Webinar: Questions and Answers</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-webinar-questions-and-answers</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 9 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>On June 6, 2016 at 10 am PDT, NathanR and myself (CareyH) introduced Komodo X to the world (just under 100 people…) in a live webcast. Our goal was to show off some of the new features in action and let people ask questions about what they heard, saw [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-webinar-questions-and-answers</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Top 11 Tips and Tricks for Komodo X</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/top-11-tips-and-tricks-for-komodo-x</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 7 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description> I would like to start this post by thanking those of you who have mild to severe OCD and yet still clicked our provocative title.   I realized while writing another blog post that we hadn’t written a Komodo Tips and Tricks post for over 3 years [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/top-11-tips-and-tricks-for-komodo-x</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>5 Reasons to use an IDE Instead of an Editor</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/5-reasons-to-use-an-ide-instead-of-an-editor</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 1 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>The word *editor* and IDE (integrated development environments) are often mistakenly used interchangeably. However, there are some big differences between the two. The extra functionality you get with an IDE can provide significant time savings [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/5-reasons-to-use-an-ide-instead-of-an-editor</guid>
            </item>
    </channel>
</rss>