<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Komodo Blogs</title>
        <description>Komodo blog RSS feed.  </description>
        <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/</link>
        <language>en</language>
        <webMaster>support@activestate.com (ActiveState Support)</webMaster>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 03:10:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Middleman 3.3.10</generator>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Extreme Makeover</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-extreme-makeover</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 6 Jul 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>If you installed Komodo X recently and you were not one of the users who participated in the Beta release phase then when you opened Komodo you might have thought you downloaded the wrong program (Chess any one?).  But you didn&#x27;t [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-extreme-makeover</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>10 Komodo Features Web Developers Will Love</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/10-komodo-features-web-developers-will-love</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo IDE X adds a ton of new features, many of which targeted at web developers. We realize that while not everyone may consider themselves a web developer, most developers these days will be using web technologies to some degree [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/10-komodo-features-web-developers-will-love</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>How We Made Komodo X Even Faster</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/how-we-made-komodo-x-even-faster</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo has always been a very fast IDE. So much so that combined with its minimalistic UI many users tend to confuse Komodo IDE with an editor. Of course Komodo is an editor too, but to call it just an editor would be doing it a disservice [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/how-we-made-komodo-x-even-faster</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 10.0.1 Released</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-0-1-released</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>We hope everyone has been enjoying Komodo X so far. Today we&#x27;re releasing our first update, which is focussed entirely on stability and primarily resolves bugs introduced in 10.0.0 as well as a few longer standing issues [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-0-1-released</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo X Webinar: Questions and Answers</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-webinar-questions-and-answers</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 9 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>On June 6, 2016 at 10 am PDT, NathanR and myself (CareyH) introduced Komodo X to the world (just under 100 people…) in a live webcast. Our goal was to show off some of the new features in action and let people ask questions about what they heard, saw [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-webinar-questions-and-answers</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Top 11 Tips and Tricks for Komodo X</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/top-11-tips-and-tricks-for-komodo-x</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 7 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description> I would like to start this post by thanking those of you who have mild to severe OCD and yet still clicked our provocative title.   I realized while writing another blog post that we hadn’t written a Komodo Tips and Tricks post for over 3 years [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/top-11-tips-and-tricks-for-komodo-x</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>5 Reasons to use an IDE Instead of an Editor</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/5-reasons-to-use-an-ide-instead-of-an-editor</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 1 Jun 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>The word *editor* and IDE (integrated development environments) are often mistakenly used interchangeably. However, there are some big differences between the two. The extra functionality you get with an IDE can provide significant time savings [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/5-reasons-to-use-an-ide-instead-of-an-editor</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Chrome Debugging in Komodo X, Code and Debug in One Place</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/chrome-debugging-in-komodo-x-code-and-debug-in-one-place</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Let me set the stage: You are a web developer. You spend many hours a week writing javascript, running javascript and debugging javascript. You&#x27;re very adept at it, you write your code, fire up a web server and point Chrome at it [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/chrome-debugging-in-komodo-x-code-and-debug-in-one-place</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo X Released - It&#x27;s 10X Better</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-released</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>The moment is finally here, Komodo X (10) is released and it&#x27;s like 10 times better! The pun sounded so horrible when I came up with it, I just had to use it. But it really is a LOT better [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-x-released</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Help Us Test Komodo IDE 10 and We&#x27;ll Give You $50</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/help-us-test-komodo-ide-10-and-well-give-you-usd50</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>As you may have heard, we released our Komodo 10 alpha last week so the community can help us run it through its paces. We&#x27;ve already received a ton of helpful bug reports but we want MORE [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/help-us-test-komodo-ide-10-and-well-give-you-usd50</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 10 Alpha Pre-release Now Available</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-alpha-pre-release-now-available</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description> Releasing an alpha&#x2F;beta of your product is like showing everyone your new baby. Everyone is excited, but he&#x27;s still very fragile, and you&#x27;re scared someone might look at them the wrong way. Komodo 10 has come a long way [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-10-alpha-pre-release-now-available</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Toolbox</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-toolbox</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 7 Apr 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>The Komodo toolbox is where you can store all of your custom tools such as code snippets and abbreviations, userscripts, commands, etc.  The fresh Komodo install comes with a huge selection of tools and snippets already installed [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-toolbox</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Go-to-Definiton</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/go-to-definition</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 5 Apr 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo Go to Definition is a helpful tool to quickly see the definition of any construct in your code.  Whether it&#x27;s a function, a variable, a class, class member or global [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/go-to-definition</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Configuring Komodo</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/configuring-komodo</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo has been written with the concept of &quot;make the best guess then allow custom changes&quot;.  For 90% of Komodo features, you should simply be able to start Komodo and use it, and it will just work.   At start up [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/configuring-komodo</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Smart Snippets</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/smart-snippets</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo snippets and abbreviations are nothing new to code editing (they&#x27;ve been in Komodo almost since the beginning 15 years ago). But something that Komodo has that others may not...smart snippets [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/smart-snippets</guid>
            </item>
    </channel>
</rss>