<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Komodo Blogs</title>
        <description>Komodo blog RSS feed.  </description>
        <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/</link>
        <language>en</language>
        <webMaster>support@activestate.com (ActiveState Support)</webMaster>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 7 Mar 2016 12:11:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Middleman 3.3.10</generator>
            <item>
                <title>Track Changes: For Programmers Who Sometimes Make Mistakes</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/track-change</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 3 Mar 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>As you may well be aware, I am an excellent programmer.  What you may not be aware of is that I SOMETIMES make mistakes.  When one of these most uncommon events occur [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/track-change</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Code Intelligence in Komodo</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/code-int</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 1 Mar 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>All of our main languages like, Python, PHP, Ruby, Perl, Javascript, NodeJS, Go, Tcl and HTML, among others have code intelligence support.   Not only does this mean that you get code intelligence for native language functions, classes [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/code-int</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo's Commando Tool</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodos-commando-tool</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo's Commando tool is a workhorse in Komodo. Through the Commando window you can access all of Komodo's internal commands, all toolbox items, open any file on your computer, find code symbols related to your file and project, etc [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodos-commando-tool</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Packages</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-packages</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>In Komodo we have a concept of Packages. A package is any external item that can be added to Komodo [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-packages</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Debugging with Komodo IDE</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/debugging-with-komodo-ide</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo supports debugging (*IDE ONLY*) for all of it's major dynamic languages which includes Python, PHP, Go, Perl, Tcl, Ruby, NodeJS and JavaScript [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/debugging-with-komodo-ide</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo UI/UX & Customization</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-ui-ux-and-customization</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 1 Feb 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Back in November, with the help of our talented marketing team, Nathan and I hosted a webinar to show our new/potential/existing users the major features of Komodo, how to use them and how to customize them. Now if you're like me [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-ui-ux-and-customization</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>JSX and React: A Komodo Syntax Highlighting Case Study</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/jsx-and-react-a-komodo-syntax-highlighting-case-study</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>An often overlooked feature in Komodo is the ability to create extensions for highlighting the syntax of new and custom languages. It seems that every week brings news of a new language on the block. The good news is that with a little bit of work [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/jsx-and-react-a-komodo-syntax-highlighting-case-study</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 9.3.2 Released</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-2-rele</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Time for another maintenance release! This release is focussed entirely on stability and resolves bugs introduced in 9.3 as well as some longer standing issues.  Most notably, this release fixed the flickering issue on OSX [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-2-rele</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo User Story: Jake Day Williams</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-user-story-jake-day-williams</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Learning a new programming language isn't easy for everyone, and there is no better place than YouTube find a good tutorial to see code in action. In your search to learn PHP or Ruby, you may have stumbled upon Jake Day Williams' channel, WiLDacademy [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-user-story-jake-day-williams</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Quick Bookmarks</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-quick-bookmarks</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 8 Dec 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>A feature that you may or may not be aware of in Komodo is the Quick Bookmarks tool.  The Quick Bookmarks extend bookmarks to make them faster to use by allowing you to access specific bookmarks with a single keystroke [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-quick-bookmarks</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo Webinar Questions</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-webinar-questions</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Some of you might have heard that Nathan and I took time out of our dev schedules to do an *Intro to Komodo* webinar on the 19th of November, 2015.  What you may not know is that everyone asked a TON of questions [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-webinar-questions</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 9.3.1 Released</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-1-released</link>
                <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Roughly 3 weeks after our release of 9.3.0 we have 9.3.1 ready for you. This release is focussed entirely on stability and resolves bugs introduced in 9.3 as well as some longer standing issues [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-1-released</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Webinar: The One IDE for all Your Needs</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/webinar-the-one-ide-for-all-your-needs</link>
                <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>Komodo has long been the ideal IDE for team development environments, in any industry and for any team size, platform, or language. We recently released Komodo 9.3, packed with tons of great new features [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/webinar-the-one-ide-for-all-your-needs</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo 9.3 Released - Yours Forever!</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-released-yours-forever</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 3 Nov 2015 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                <description>It's finally here, possibly our most major minor release ever - Komodo 9.3. There is so much in this release we could almost have called it Komodo 10, but we didn't [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-9-3-released-yours-forever</guid>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Komodo IDE User Story: Defman</title>
                <link>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-ide-user-story-defman</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
                <description>I love the diversity of our users. We've featured prior user stories with developers who first learned to program using FORTRAN or BASIC. Today's story features a Komodo user on the opposite end of that spectrum [...]</description>
                <guid>http://komodoide.com/blog/komodo-ide-user-story-defman</guid>
            </item>
    </channel>
</rss>